<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Traffic App</string>
    <string name="Simulation_algorithms"><u><b><i>Simulation algorithms</i></b></u></string>
    <string name="Simulation_Calibrations"><u><b><i>Simulation Calibrations</i></b></u></string>
    <string name="Simulation_History"><u><b><i>Simulation History and Stats</i></b></u></string>
    <string name="back"><u><b><i>Back</i></b></u></string>
    <string name="register"><u><b><i>Don\'t have an account? Register here</i></b></u></string>
    <string name="login"><u><b><i>Already have an account? Login here</i></b></u></string>
    <string name="password"><u><b><i>Forgot your password? Reset it here</i></b></u></string>
    <string name="alg_exp1">
        \tIn this section, we will discuss the logic behind the application\'s main
    functionality displayed in the <b>simulation</b> page.\n
    \tWhen you click the <b>run simulation</b> button, a number of background processes are
        simultaneously started:\n
        <b>-</b> The <b>lane_add_threads</b> and the
    <b>lane_sub_threads</b> that periodically add and subtract traffic density
        to the lanes at the rate of one density point per second at the intervals
    defined by the user in the <b>simulation settings</b> page.\n
        <b>-</b> The <b>control_traffic_light_thread</b> that periodically sets a specific
        light in the control diagram to orange, green then red in a predefined order at intervals defined by the
        user in the <b>simulation settings</b> page.\n
        <b>-</b> The <b>ai_traffic_light_thread</b> that periodically sets a specific
        light in the adaptable diagram to orange, green then red in a order that is
        decided by the A.I algorithm. The algorithm used is the Random Forest Algorithm.
        The A.I model is fed a set of density values from all the lanes in the junction
        during the simulation at short intervals. The algorithm then predicts which light
        to turn red/green based on the input. The A.I predictions are further processed
        based on some extra parameters such as how long a light has gone without being green.\n
        <b>-</b> The <b>junction_efficiency_threads</b> that periodically capture the
        average traffic density of a junction and creates an array pair with the timestamp
        of when the capture occurred. Additionally, the average of all averages of density captures
        is calculated when the simulation ends. This values are captured for both the control and the
        adaptable version at the same time. The average of all averages is then used to compute the
        efficiency rating of the adaptable traffic coordination which is seen as a percentage
        in either green(more efficient than control) or red(less efficient than control) in the <b>history</b> page.\n
    </string>
    <string name="calibrations_exp1">
        \tIn this section, we will discuss the different simulation settings one can alter
        in the <b>simulation</b> page, <b>simulation settings</b> page and the <b>custom traffic</b> page.\n
        <b>- Light duration times: </b> These settings set the duration in which a certain colour will be displayed.
        Apart from the orange light time which applies for both the control and the A.I simulation variants,
        these settings are only for the control simulation.\n
        <b>- Density increase time: </b> This setting set the interval between traffic density
        changes for all lanes and for both the control and A.I simulation variants.\n
        <b>- Custom traffic (YouTube links): </b> These settings initiate a <b>video_saving_and_car_detection</b> thread that
        downloads the traffic footage from YouTube to the devices internal storage and extracts frames from the footage
        at a rate defined in the frame interval setting. A car detection algorithm using
        cascades classifier is run on these frames and the car count is then saved in the
        users settings and retrieved when the <b>custom</b> setting in the <b>traffic density</b> dropdown,
        in the <b>simulations</b> page, is chosen. The frames are deleted after the density values
        are gotten from them\n
        <b>- Frames extracted per second: </b> This setting determine the number of frames
        extracted from the footage per second.\n
        <b>- Junction type: </b> This setting determines the junction type used in the
        simulation.\n
        <b>- Traffic Density type: </b> This setting determines the traffic density type used in the
        simulation.\n
    </string>
    <string name="stats_exp1">
        \tIn this section, we will discuss how to interpret the information displayed
        in the <b>history</b> page and the <b>simulation stats</b> page.\n\n
        <u><b>History Page </b></u> \n
        \tin this page, we can see the list of all of a user\'s past simulations ordered by
        date of occurrence. The individual list elements have the junction type in white
        text, the density type in grey below the junction type, the efficiency rating
        of the adaptable simulation variant in red(if the A.I was less efficient
        than the control) or green(if the A.I was more efficient
        than the control) and finally the time the simulation was run below the
        efficiency rating.\n
        One can simply delete a simulation by swiping it off the screen.\n\n
        <u><b>Simulation Stats Page </b></u> \n
        \tin this page, we can see the a graphical representation of a simulation\'s
        performance and below that, all the settings with which the simulation was run.\n
        \tThe graph has the average density of the junction on the y axis and the timestamp
        at which the density was captured on the x axis. The graph plots the points for the
        A.I and the control variants on the same canvas for comparison.
    </string>
    <string-array name="junctionTypes">
        <item>T junction</item>
        <item>Roundabout</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="densityTypes">
        <item>Randomized</item>
<!--        <item>Heavy Traffic</item>-->
<!--        <item>Light Traffic</item>-->
        <item>Custom</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="timingTypes">
        <item>Default</item>
        <item>Custom</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="orangeTimings">
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="densityTimings">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>25</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>35</item>
        <item>40</item>
        <item>45</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>55</item>
        <item>60</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>